MUD1/British Legends source code, 1999-2014 M2013
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
MUD1/British Legends source code
1992-2014
M2013
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
50.0 computer file(s) (50 files in 3 directories)
Arrangement note
There are 50 files in 3 directories. Only the files in the DATABASE directory are listed in this guide.
Access to Collection
Files are open for research but are only available through the media cart (dedicated offline computers) in the Special Collections' reading room.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given by Viktor Toth to Stanford University, Special Collections in 2014.
Related collection
Richard Bartle papers, 1979-1997
Scope and Contents
This implementation of MUD (Multi-User Dungeon) was developed and is operated by Viktor T. Toth. MUD1 was originally developed circa 1978 at Essex University, England. This version runs on 32-bit platforms; the current server runs on Windows and Linux (2014).
Toth, Viktor (Viktor T.); Computer files; Computer games--History.; History of Science; Software -- Application development
- 1. 05/29/2014 12:49 PM [directory]
  Scope and Contents
  21 files including the directory file (428,694 bytes).
  - 10/02/2011 07:56 AM 68,676 game.cpp
  - 10/16/2011 04:43 PM 17,877 game.h
  - 05/23/2014 04:44 PM 2,152 main.cpp
  - 10/27/2008 05:30 AM 542 Makefile
  - 03/12/2010 05:21 PM 553 Makefile64
  - 10/27/2008 05:36 AM 10,941 mud1.cpp
  - 12/22/1999 12:03 AM 531 MUD1.DSW
  - 10/16/2011 04:45 PM 5,386 mud1.h
  - 11/09/2003 11:14 AM 9,799 MUD1.mak
  - 11/07/2003 03:28 PM 2,667 MUD1.RC
  - 09/26/2011 06:42 PM 13,330 persfile.cpp
  - 10/16/2011 04:43 PM 3,662 persfile.h
  - 10/16/2011 04:43 PM 393 resource.h
  - 12/26/1999 10:38 PM 4,817 SERVICE.H
  - 01/08/2013 06:10 AM 255,661 slot.cpp
  - 10/16/2011 04:43 PM 15,638 slot.h
  - 08/05/2001 10:58 AM 207 stdhdr.cpp
  - 10/16/2011 04:43 PM 788 stdhdr.h
  - 05/10/2009 04:07 AM 12,347 util.cpp
  - 10/16/2011 04:43 PM 2,727 util.h
- 2. 05/29/2014 12:49 PM [directory].
- 3. 05/29/2014 08:30 AM [directory] DATABASE
  There are 30 files in this directory.